submitprowith.us 2016-11-24

# SubmitPRO - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is the most important thing for us. We feel the duty to express ourselfs about the safety policy that we have, in order to explain our customers how the use of your information will be dealt with. This information is available in every section of our site that requires any information of your personal identification.

## Google Adsense/DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google is a third-party vendor and it uses cookies to provide the ads on this site as long as all the other sites it has under it. Only by the use of DART cookies they're able to provide such interest-based service. To opt out of the interest-based advertising please follow this link: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. The traking methods used by Google are subject of Google's own privacy policy, please refer to that. Several other third-party ad networks may also use the same method to track trend activities.

## The Use of Personal Information

The information used to analyze trends is saved along with the IP adress, dates and times of the visit. This information can be used to track users movement to set demografic graphics, administer the website, decide marketing strategies and etc. All this information is only for internal usage and it's not, in any way, related to your personal information.

## As for this Privacy Statement

The content of this privacy statement can be altered at any given time, we advice user discretion. If you have any doubts regarding our privacy policy please contact us here.
